本字幕由天满宫字幕组制作，翻译:neko，字幕:neko 校对:neko，cinewamage，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
What the hell you two doing?
你们两个在干啥嘞？
Get your ass down from here now, boy!
赶快给我滚下来，小子！
And you too, someone or something got you excited, son?
你也是，是谁或什么让你们兴奋，孩子？
No, sir!
没有，长官！
You're lying to me.
你小子骗我
I saw you looking over at your pretty boy recruit over here getting turned on.
我看到你对着漂亮男孩新兵而感到兴奋。
Yes, sir. No, sir.
是，长官，真的没有，长官
All of you, get your asses down here now!
你们所有人，现在就下来！
Attention!
给我立正站好！
What the hell do you boys think that this is, fucking fairyland?
你们把这里他妈的当成仙境了吗？
Pulling on your wee-wees like a pack of fucking fruits?
就像他妈的一群男同一样吸着肉棒？
You two obviously want to suck what a real man has,
你们两个显然想要吸一个真男人的东西，
so get down on your knees and suck every last drop of my cum
所以跪下来，吸干我所有的精液，
until my dick is drained.
直到我的肉棒被榨干。
Now!
现在！
Disobedience, huh?
不服从，嗯？
That's a mistake.
那将是你们的错误
Get to the quarterdeck, now!
赶快给我到甲板上！
Move, move, move!
动起来，快，快！
You two, get over here and service your DI's cock.
你们两个，过来为你们的教官服♂务。
Now!
立刻！
Ah, it feels hot
啊，感觉好热。
Yeah, work that tool.
对，好好使用那个工具。
That's right, I'm gonna teach you to be a man.
没错，我会教你成为一个男人。
That's right.
没错
Ah, it feels hot
啊，感觉好热。
I'm gonna cum all over your face
我想要射在你的脸上。
I want you to pull it out and jerk it off all over the pretty lips.
我想要用你漂亮的嘴帮我吸出来
Okay, maggots.
好的，蛆虫们
I want to see six hot loads
现在我想看到六发热烈的炮♂弹
on your DI's hat, now.
打在你们的长官的帽子上